let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "vertra\u00fcnw\u00fcrdig", "answer": "trustworthy", "options": ["trustworthy", "city treasuries", "thrilling", "certificate,report"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "L\u00e4rm", "answer": "Noise", "options": ["to be fixed", "external", "Valueables", "Noise"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "m\u00f6glicherweise", "answer": "possibly", "options": ["possibly", "constantly, always", "residence", "suffered"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "st\u00e4ndig", "answer": "constantly, always", "options": ["receipt, revenue", "constantly, always", "Carried together", "popularity"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Leistungen", "answer": "achievements", "options": ["stressful", "train rides", "hazard", "achievements"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Schon_lange", "answer": "long time", "options": ["long time", "railing", "traffic noise", "tiring,exhausting"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "exotisch", "answer": "exotic", "options": ["exotic", "diversification", "carrier choice", "showman"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "Startseite", "answer": "Home page", "options": ["uses", "railing", "original", "Home page"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Teppiche", "answer": "carpets, rugs", "options": ["Heart attack", "carpets, rugs", "strong hold", "time"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Gefahr", "answer": "hazard", "options": ["whisper, pisumatu", "Current", "hazard", "more sensitive"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Umst\u00e4ndlich", "answer": "laborious, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0caf\u0cbe\u0cb8\u0c95\u0cb0", "options": ["laborious, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0caf\u0cbe\u0cb8\u0c95\u0cb0", "achievements", "certificate,report", "railing"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "answer": "basically", "options": ["lucky number", "basically", "traffic noise", "heading"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Bewertungen", "answer": "Valuation", "options": ["receipt, revenue", "Spiritual, \u0c86\u0ca7\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cae\u0cbf\u0c95", "rare", "Valuation"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "H\u00f6rst\u00f6rungen", "answer": "heart disorder", "options": ["Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "heart disorder", "suffered", "just like that"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "empfindlichen", "answer": "sensitive", "options": ["sensitive", "irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "trustworthy", "uses"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "wertsachen", "answer": "Valueables", "options": ["Orphan", "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "Valueables", "coming school"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "\u00fcbrig", "answer": "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6", "options": ["Profittable", "superficial, \u0cac\u0cbe\u0cb9\u0ccd\u0caf, \u0cb9\u0cc1\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb2\u0ccd\u0cb2\u0ca6", "showman", "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "dennoch", "answer": "yet,still", "options": ["slight, minor", "Public festival", "Noise", "yet,still"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "eillig", "answer": "hurry, urgent", "options": ["almost", "hurry, urgent", "residence", "spectator"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Hauptverkehrstra\u00dfe", "answer": "main road", "options": ["fairplace", "trade certificate", "main road", "to be fixed"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Tiefe", "answer": "deep", "options": ["deep", "disturbing", "Noise", "lottery ticket"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "kopfh\u00f6rer", "answer": "headphone", "options": ["self evident", "popularity", "headphone", "complaints"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Verkehrsl\u00e4rm", "answer": "traffic noise", "options": ["extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf", "self evident", "hearing nerve", "traffic noise"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Selbverst\u00e4ndlich", "answer": "self evident", "options": ["constantly, always", "Rich values", "self evident", "basically"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "irgendwann", "answer": "somewhere", "options": ["exotic", "somewhere", "Subject, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0cb7\u0caf", "stressful"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Zuschauer", "answer": "spectator", "options": ["Carried together", "governed", "spectator", "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Volkfest", "answer": "Public festival", "options": ["Carried together", "fairplace", "sensitive", "Public festival"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "berufst\u00e4tig", "answer": "professional, working", "options": ["professional, working", "constantly, always", "strong hold", "tiring,exhausting"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "Bahnfahten", "answer": "train rides", "options": ["even, yet", "slide", "sound proof windows", "train rides"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "ger\u00e4usche", "answer": "Noise", "options": ["external", "Noise", "News portals", "train rides"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "Berufswahl", "answer": "carrier choice", "options": ["possibly", "pullen", "carrier choice", "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "genauso", "answer": "just like that", "options": ["sensitive", "van, Caravan", "just like that", "thrilling"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "Wohlbefinden", "answer": "well being", "options": ["receipt, revenue", "company owner", "just like that", "well being"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "zugang", "answer": "Access", "options": ["slide", "Access", "headphone", "Resposibility"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "herum", "answer": "almost", "options": ["somewhere", "News portals", "current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8", "almost"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "st\u00f6rend", "answer": "disturbing", "options": ["Public festival", "disturbing", "external", "uses"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "H\u00f6rnerven", "answer": "hearing nerve", "options": ["sensitive", "Civic, Citizen", "hearing nerve", "self evident"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "Rauscht", "answer": "whisper, pisumatu", "options": ["whisper, pisumatu", "house rules", "failure", "suffered"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "Rasen", "answer": "Races,\u0c9c\u0ca8\u0cbe\u0ce6\u0c97 (not fast speed race)", "options": ["Civic, Citizen", "Races,\u0c9c\u0ca8\u0cbe\u0ce6\u0c97 (not fast speed race)", "more sensitive", "overall"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "gering", "answer": "slight, minor", "options": ["Noise", "deep", "van, Caravan", "slight, minor"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "\u00c4u\u00dferungen", "answer": "expression", "options": ["mainly", "level", "professional, working", "expression"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "externen", "answer": "external", "options": ["remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6", "external", "irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "well being"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "Tagesablauf", "answer": "daily routine", "options": ["house rules", "traffic noise", "lucky number", "daily routine"]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "sogar", "answer": "even, yet", "options": ["lucky number", "even, yet", "house rules", "News portals"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "plant, enterprize", "options": ["front door", "everywhere", "alaram clock ring", "plant, enterprize"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "los", "answer": "fate,destiny", "options": ["original", "more difficulty", "final exam", "fate,destiny"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "gewinnbringende", "answer": "Profittable", "options": ["constantly, always", "strong hold", "Profittable", "van, Caravan"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "Medientag", "answer": "Media Day", "options": ["Media Day", "just like that", "almost", "more sensitive"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "staatkassen", "answer": "city treasuries", "options": ["more difficulty", "lucky number", "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "city treasuries"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "selten", "answer": "rare", "options": ["hurry, urgent", "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6", "yet,still", "rare"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "\u00dcberall", "answer": "everywhere", "options": ["everywhere", "Access", "Valueables", "fate,destiny"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "L\u00e4rmveraursacher", "answer": "noise pollution", "options": ["suffered", "noise pollution", "slight, minor", "all the rest"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "misserfolg", "answer": "failure", "options": ["expression", "pullen", "failure", "Contents"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "Ver\u00e4nderungen", "answer": "diversification", "options": ["whisper, pisumatu", "diversification", "train rides", "front door"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "Verwendet", "answer": "uses", "options": ["constantly, always", "everywhere", "uses", "original"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "Einnahmen", "answer": "receipt, revenue", "options": ["hurry, urgent", "constantly, always", "possibly", "receipt, revenue"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "schausteller", "answer": "showman", "options": ["showman", "long time", "Carried together", "governed"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "festen", "answer": "strong hold", "options": ["hearing nerve", "strong hold", "Night peace", "more sensitive"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "weckerlingeln", "answer": "alaram clock ring", "options": ["back then", "Unsettled life", "alaram clock ring", "Public festival"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "Mitglieder", "answer": "members", "options": ["Rich values", "stress triggers", "thrilling", "members"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "Volkfestplatz", "answer": "fairplace", "options": ["fairplace", "main road", "hazard", "final exam"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "Beschwerden", "answer": "complaints", "options": ["complaints", "house rules", "Race, speed race", "everywhere"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "Gewerbschein", "answer": "trade certificate", "options": ["suffered", "even, yet", "trade certificate", "governed"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "so_gut_wie_gar", "answer": "almost not at all", "options": ["Night peace", "time eater", "almost not at all", "lottery ticket"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "damals", "answer": "back then", "options": ["back then", "traffic noise", "Orphan", "train rides"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "Gl\u00fcckzahlen", "answer": "lucky number", "options": ["lucky number", "sound proof windows", "company owner", "Current"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "L\u00e4rmbelastigung", "answer": "noise pollution", "options": ["level", "noise pollution", "superficial, \u0cac\u0cbe\u0cb9\u0ccd\u0caf, \u0cb9\u0cc1\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb2\u0ccd\u0cb2\u0ca6", "durable, permanent"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "Abschlusspr\u00fcfung", "answer": "final exam", "options": ["final exam", "hours long", "Unsettled life", "more difficulty"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "spannende", "answer": "thrilling", "options": ["thrilling", "stress triggers", "Civic, Citizen", "exceptionally"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "stundenlang", "answer": "hours long", "options": ["hours long", "term", "receipt, revenue", "thrilling"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "Firmeninhaber", "answer": "company owner", "options": ["slight, minor", "Heart attack", "company owner", "extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "Belibtheit", "answer": "popularity", "options": ["Access", "popularity", "Profittable", "somewhere"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "zettel", "answer": "slip, note, bill, \u0c9a\u0cc0\u0c9f\u0cbf", "options": ["Race, speed race", "slip, note, bill, \u0c9a\u0cc0\u0c9f\u0cbf", "suffered", "laborious, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0caf\u0cbe\u0cb8\u0c95\u0cb0"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "schweringen", "answer": "more difficulty", "options": ["spectator", "basically", "more difficulty", "Departure"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "Stressausl\u00f6sen", "answer": "stress triggers", "options": ["stress triggers", "almost", "just like that", "mainly"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "Inhaltverzeichnis", "answer": "Contents", "options": ["even, yet", "main road", "Contents", "Breakfast Table"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "Abreise", "answer": "Departure", "options": ["Departure", "certificate,report", "diversification", "hearing nerve"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "Hausordnung", "answer": "house rules", "options": ["house rules", "wild fire", "trade certificate", "external"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "Tippschein", "answer": "lottery ticket", "options": ["lottery ticket", "everywhere", "hazard", "railing"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "zeiten", "answer": "time", "options": ["time", "Contents", "heading", "hurry, urgent"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "Gel\u00e4nder", "answer": "railing", "options": ["term", "railing", "plant, enterprize", "heart disorder"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "Nachrichtsportale", "answer": "News portals", "options": ["mainly", "house rules", "van, Caravan", "News portals"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "ausnahmeweise", "answer": "exceptionally", "options": ["Noise", "exceptionally", "Rich values", "house rules"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "fr\u00fchst\u00fcckstich", "answer": "Breakfast Table", "options": ["lottery ticket", "Valuation", "Breakfast Table", "self evident"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "feststehen", "answer": "to be fixed", "options": ["carrier choice", "to be fixed", "constantly, always", "current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "waisenkind", "answer": "Orphan", "options": ["current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8", "replacer", "hazard", "Orphan"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "seelisches", "answer": "Spiritual, \u0c86\u0ca7\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cae\u0cbf\u0c95", "options": ["durable, permanent", "expression", "Spiritual, \u0c86\u0ca7\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0ca4\u0ccd\u0cae\u0cbf\u0c95", "Heart attack"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "Reichwerte", "answer": "Rich values", "options": ["railing", "Rich values", "everywhere", "alaram clock ring"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "Rassen", "answer": "Race, speed race", "options": ["train rides", "Public festival", "possibly", "Race, speed race"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "Zusammengetragen", "answer": "Carried together", "options": ["Carried together", "even, yet", "triangle", "Night peace"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "eingebu\u00dft", "answer": "suffered", "options": ["Night peace", "noise pollution", "suffered", "tiring,exhausting"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "Berghof", "answer": "ward", "options": ["term", "carrier choice", "Heart attack", "ward"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "Zeitgeschehen", "answer": "current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8", "options": ["carrier choice", "durable, permanent", "well", "current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "gesamten", "answer": "overall", "options": ["replacer", "overall", "Noise", "fairplace"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "Haust\u00fcr", "answer": "front door", "options": ["front door", "thrilling", "daily routine", "governed"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "zeitfresser", "answer": "time eater", "options": ["original", "slide", "daily routine", "time eater"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "zogen", "answer": "pullen", "options": ["current affairs, \u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0c9a\u0cb2\u0cbf\u0ca4 \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0ca6\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cae\u0cbe\u0ca8", "pullen", "front door", "durable, permanent"]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "ersetzer", "answer": "replacer", "options": ["lottery ticket", "stress triggers", "replacer", "strong hold"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "\u00fcbringen", "answer": "all the rest", "options": ["Orphan", "stress triggers", "all the rest", "company owner"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "Lautst\u00e4rke", "answer": "volume, loudness", "options": ["disturbing", "fairplace", "well being", "volume, loudness"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "oberfl\u00e4chlich", "answer": "superficial, \u0cac\u0cbe\u0cb9\u0ccd\u0caf, \u0cb9\u0cc1\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb2\u0ccd\u0cb2\u0ca6", "options": ["constantly, always", "time", "Orphan", "superficial, \u0cac\u0cbe\u0cb9\u0ccd\u0caf, \u0cb9\u0cc1\u0cb0\u0cc1\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0cb2\u0ccd\u0cb2\u0ca6"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "Herzinfarkt", "answer": "Heart attack", "options": ["all the rest", "Departure", "somewhere", "Heart attack"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "wohnwagen", "answer": "van, Caravan", "options": ["Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "alaram clock ring", "van, Caravan", "hours long"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "Aktuell", "answer": "Current", "options": ["self evident", "plant, enterprize", "Current", "governed"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "ausgiebig", "answer": "extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf", "options": ["ward", "hearing nerve", "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "begriff", "answer": "term", "options": ["railing", "term", "Contents", "even"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "Betreff", "answer": "Subject, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0cb7\u0caf", "options": ["Subject, \u0cb5\u0cbf\u0cb7\u0caf", "all the rest", "daily routine", "hearing nerve"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "anstrenged", "answer": "tiring,exhausting", "options": ["trade certificate", "tiring,exhausting", "somewhere", "professional, working"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "sensibler", "answer": "more sensitive", "options": ["failure", "more sensitive", "all the rest", "term"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "Belastend", "answer": "stressful", "options": ["exceptionally", "stressful", "hours long", "well being"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "Dreieck", "answer": "triangle", "options": ["triangle", "trade certificate", "transmissions", "self evident"]}, {"numb": 112, "question": "Volksport", "answer": "national sport", "options": ["main road", "durable, permanent", "volume, loudness", "national sport"]}, {"numb": 113, "question": "schallschutzfenster", "answer": "sound proof windows", "options": ["city treasuries", "Resposibility", "sound proof windows", "tiring,exhausting"]}, {"numb": 114, "question": "verantwortung", "answer": "Resposibility", "options": ["more sensitive", "external", "Resposibility", "Civic, Citizen"]}, {"numb": 115, "question": "wohl", "answer": "well", "options": ["irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "company owner", "whisper, pisumatu", "well"]}, {"numb": 116, "question": "donnert", "answer": "thunder", "options": ["thunder", "complaints", "triangle", "original"]}, {"numb": 117, "question": "\u00dcberschrift", "answer": "heading", "options": ["heading", "coming school", "hours long", "Unsettled life"]}, {"numb": 118, "question": "Gang", "answer": "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "options": ["almost not at all", "Race, speed race", "Passage, \u0cae\u0cbe\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0c97", "even, yet"]}, {"numb": 119, "question": "Nachtruhe", "answer": "Night peace", "options": ["Night peace", "suffered", "spectator", "constantly, always"]}, {"numb": 120, "question": "Lauffeuer", "answer": "wild fire", "options": ["wild fire", "yet,still", "whisper, pisumatu", "Access"]}, {"numb": 121, "question": "stammschule", "answer": "coming school", "options": ["coming school", "overall", "company owner", "extensive,substantial, \u0c97\u0ca3\u0ca8\u0cc0\u0caf, \u0cb5\u0ccd\u0caf\u0cbe\u0caa\u0c95\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0c97\u0cbf"]}, {"numb": 122, "question": "B\u00fcrger", "answer": "Civic, Citizen", "options": ["hurry, urgent", "popularity", "Civic, Citizen", "tiring,exhausting"]}, {"numb": 123, "question": "eben", "answer": "even", "options": ["failure", "daily routine", "Races,\u0c9c\u0ca8\u0cbe\u0ce6\u0c97 (not fast speed race)", "even"]}, {"numb": 124, "question": "Niveau", "answer": "level", "options": ["diversification", "receipt, revenue", "ward", "level"]}, {"numb": 125, "question": "unerheblich", "answer": "irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "options": ["ward", "irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "even, yet", "hazard"]}, {"numb": 126, "question": "wanderleben", "answer": "Unsettled life", "options": ["Unsettled life", "house rules", "well", "hurry, urgent"]}, {"numb": 127, "question": "wohnsitz", "answer": "residence", "options": ["residence", "just like that", "tiring,exhausting", "hours long"]}, {"numb": 128, "question": "Rutsche", "answer": "slide", "options": ["irrelevant \u0c85\u0caa\u0ccd\u0cb0\u0cb8\u0ccd\u0ca4\u0cc1\u0ca4", "slide", "governed", "overall"]}, {"numb": 129, "question": "geregelten", "answer": "governed", "options": ["governed", "Valuation", "Public festival", "volume, loudness"]}, {"numb": 130, "question": "dauerhaft", "answer": "durable, permanent", "options": ["overall", "almost not at all", "exotic", "durable, permanent"]}, {"numb": 131, "question": "urspr\u00fcnglich", "answer": "original", "options": ["original", "complaints", "time eater", "remaning, \u0c89\u0cb3\u0cbf\u0ca6"]}, {"numb": 132, "question": "zeugnis", "answer": "certificate,report", "options": ["hearing nerve", "back then", "certificate,report", "almost"]}, {"numb": 133, "question": "haupts\u00e4chlich", "answer": "mainly", "options": ["back then", "mainly", "pullen", "thunder"]}, {"numb": 134, "question": "\u00fcbertragungen", "answer": "transmissions", "options": ["hearing nerve", "almost not at all", "transmissions", "volume, loudness"]}];